Good morning, sir.
You've been mugged.
Wow! Onigiri!
Bon appétit!
Isn't it refreshing?
So refreshing! There's yogurt in it, too.
Good morning.
It's the second morning.
It's brighter than yesterday.
It's brighter, but yesterday
The sun
It is, isn't it?
Oh, this morning
I was so sleepy!
I'm going to have breakfast with Aki-chan now.
I'm off!
I've smashed my face.
Someone's getting smoked.
Over there...
Who's there?
Oh, shit!
Who's...
Who?Who's there?
He's sucking my dick.
But I think it's already sucking.
Really?
I just fought with Kato.
I was sweating.
It was like a bang.
I've got about 10 hits on him, Leon, and I can't hit him at all.
Thank you.
I stopped the rocks.
Oh, shit.
Someone got sucked up.
Like this or someone.
Oh, my God.
Just when I thought it couldn't get any worse, there were two of them.
There were two of them?
Oh, my God.
I don't want to see human blood.
I don't like it.
It's Yuda.
There's another one?
I don't like that.
Oh, by the way, today's bus-mates are...
Hyo-rin and...With Hyorin
Akichan
She's so cute!
Seriously, Aki-chan and I are in love at 6 o'clock.
They're so in love.
I like your room.
Hey, were you there last night? Yeah?
There's another one?
Yes!
Did you do it?
With a plastic bottle?
Yes!
That's great.
You know, yesterday,
Kanomi..,
Did they send yesterday's police box?
We had a conversation.
Police box?
I don't think so.
I can hear everything.
I heard everything.
Where did you hear it from?
Like, what's wrong with me?
I'm not talking about that.That's not what I'm talking about.
Please.
That's all I heard.
I was in the bathtub and I heard everything.
I could hear everything.
I could hear you laughing.
I heard you taking a shower.
We took a bath together.
We didn't take a bath together.
While Kanami was filming for YouTube.
While Kanami was filming for YouTube, I was taking a bath.
And I introduced our products while you were taking a bath.
Kanamin stands out for the rest of her life!
There was so much stuff in the suitcases.
Half of them were souvenirs.
The suitcase was full of cute souvenirs!
It was overflowing with cute souvenirs.
Well, let's do our best again today, shall we?
Today we have to do the dance first.
I'll do my best!
Let's go, let's go!
Oh! What?
Listen up! Oh, the theater!
Oh, yeah! This is it!
Oh, my God! This is it? Wow!Oh! This is it? Wow!
Wall-sies! Wall-service vehicle!
Wow!
Wow.
Hi! Hiyori!
Oh! Yaaaay!
Hiy! Akki!
Enank?
Enank!
Are you hungry?
I'm so hungry!
Hibiscus tea.
Ooh!
Oh, berries? Herbscus?
Berries?
Berry berry berry
Berry, berry, berry.
What's this?
hamburger
cheeseburger
Potato
Fries?
Burger?
Cheese.cheese
Cheese?
Oh!
Very tasty.
Very delicious.
Bon appétit!
Lunch is a hamburger.
This is a cheeseburger from Burger King
Cheeseburger from Burger King in Indonesia!
It's so tiny!
I thought it would be big!
Surprisingly
The bread is sweet.
Is it sweet?
Sweet.
Yum!
OK!
Now, tomorrow's show.
This is our stage?
There's a few of them, right?
It's really cool to see a lot of people on the bill.
Kyoto stage and Tokyo
It's cute.
A little bit.
I'm going to get a haircut.Let's get a haircut.
Not exactly the same?
No, almost.
I'm so excited!
Press Conference
Wow, that's something, isn't it?
It's the first time we've ever done that.
I've never done anything like that before.
Let's work hard this afternoon.
I'll do my best.
Oh, it was the other way around.
Good night.
Mr. Okun, I'm here for a snack.
Okkun, I'm here for a snack.
What's so spicy?
There's soda in it.
And there's Ramune in it.
Peak of Ramune
Eh, I want fried shrimp!
Wow!
I want some of that, like, Chinese rice bowl.
What's that?
Yes...
I want some of this!Eh, I want to eat this.
And some fruit.
I'm so happy!
Time to fix up.
Thank you for your time.
Good night.
Good evening.
I just realized it's nighttime.
I changed into my casual clothes.
Isn't she pretty?
Denim.
Cute.
Outfits
Cute
Pannier
Cute.
I'm off to dinner now.
Bye-bye.
We did good today. Good, good, good.
Good job.
We did it! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!Yes! Yes!
Yes! Kawachan!
If you do it!
When I pressed it, it just popped.
I was so surprised.
I just wanted to get the pattern.
I've got something I really want to do.
It's an Indonesian night.
What time is it?
8:00? It's 10:00 in Japan.
Right.
It's so urban here.
Did you see it? The night view.
I saw it! I saw it!
And there was so much traffic.
What's with the masker?
A parrot.
It's really a parrot!
I'm going to eat dinner now!
It's already dark!
Let's go!
Let's go to dinner!
Say-yo!
Is this it?
Okay, thank you!OK! Thank you!
Wait!
Wow! That looks good!
Yummy? Yummy!
Ya!
This is from the last 7 to 9 years.
Oh! There's my e-mail!
Thank you!
Ha-ha-ha!
Smell good! Feels good!
Yummy!
They're not all sold out or anything.
You're right. Wait a minute.
I don't drink.
I'm here for dinner.
Coconut juice.
Here it comes!
Last sip!
Basner!
Cheers!
Bassner!
Cheers!Cheers!
Cheers!
Bon appétit!
It's like yogurt.
It's refreshing and delicious.
It's pretty refreshing, isn't it?
It's like a refreshing yogurt.
Easy to drink
Easy to drink.
Congratulations!
Melon fruit
One more came this way.
Bon appétit.
Can I eat it?
Yum.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Enark.
Filming rickey more zooань gelmans. lol
Actually, Tsuda-san took the kitchen at DoReMi and did the investment.
I'm honestly not into it.
I had to accept the contribution.I've accepted your submission.
Goodbye.
Hey there!
I bought so many souvenirs yesterday, but I didn't need them.
I bought some more!
A Nutella one and...
And cookies from Indonesia.
They don't sell them in other countries.
That's good.
Ice cream!
Oh!
Berry berry delicious!
Oh, this is M ice cream.
I heard it's good.
Is it famous?
You can't get it in Japan.
Let's try it!
I'll eat it.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm back at the hotel now!
I just came back to the hotel.
It's already night.
It's already 11 o'clock.It's almost 11:00.
It's already late.
I'm going to sleep with Aki-chan again today, but in a different hotel.
I'm going to bed together.
See you later!
I worked hard all day!
I'll do my best tomorrow, too.
Good night.